centrepointstores.com 2017-09-26

# Online Shopping at Centrepoint

RNA Resources Group Limited, a company incorporated under the laws of British Virgin Islands (referred to herein as "Centrepoint", "we", "our" or "us") is committed to protecting your privacy online. This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for participating websites of Centrepoint and its affiliated companies, currently comprising of [www.maxfashion.com](http://www.maxfashion.com/), [www.lifestyleshops.com](http://www.lifestyleshops.com/), [www.homecentre.com](https://www.homecentre.com/), [www.splashfashions.com](http://www.splashfashions.com/), [www.babyshopstores.com](http://www.babyshopstores.com/), [www.centrepointstores.com](https://www.centrepointstores.com/) and [www.shoemartstores.com](http://www.shoemartstores.com/) and their related sub-domains, sites, services and tools, or any successor site (jointly or severally referred as "Participating Website", as the context so require). The number of Participating Website may also vary in the course of time. This Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") describes the ways in which we collect, store, use and protect the information collected due to your use of Participating Website. By providing us with your information you expressly consent to us processing your personal information in accordance with the terms of the Privacy Policy.

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR PARTICIPATING WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR PARTICIPATING WEBSITE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE PARTICIPATING WEBSITE.**

  1. **Change in the Privacy Policy:** Changes in law or changes in Centrepoint’s business may require changes to be made to the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time so Centrepoint encourages you to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any such changes. It is your responsibility to carefully read, agree with the Privacy Policy on each occasion you use the Participating Website and your continued use of the Participating Website shall signify your acceptance to be bound by the latest Privacy Policy.

  2. **Single Sign On:** Each of our Participating Website offer a single-sign-on i.e. after a one-time registration on one of the Participating Website, you can sign on (login) to each of the Participating Website with uniform credentials, without having to go through a separate registration and sign-on process each time. (“Single- Sign-On”). Single- Sign-On provides a single identity - the basis for Participating Website you wish to use recognizing and verifying you. Further after logging into any of our Participating Website you can easily visit any or all of our Participating Website through links in the Participating Website. You can update your account data at any time.

  3. The Information we collect about you may be broadly described in following categories: 

    1. **Personal Information:** Your name, address, phone number, email address, user name, password, billing and credit card information, order history, feedback, IP address and location, digital device name, type and configuration, details relating to your download of Publications via the Service (including details relating to the time of the download, any interruptions, and the success or failure of the downloads), the URL from which you accessed the Participating Website, demographic information, and other such 'Personal Information'.
    2. **General Information:** We also receive more general information from you as a result of your visits to, and use of, the Participating Website. This general information does not identify you personally, and can include information such as your IP address, the length of time you spend on the Participating Website, your browsing history, and other such 'General Information'.

  4. **Treatment of Personal Information:**  

    1. For the purpose of Single- Sign-On, certain personal data is stored centrally in a database and is available to our affiliates and service providers connected with the operation of Participating Websites .
    2. Centrepoint collects your Personal Information to enable us, amongst other things, to provide the Participating Website and our Services to you. We take all steps reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorised access, use, alteration, disclosure or destruction of Personal Information. If Centrepoint is sold to a third party, or Centrepoint otherwise becomes subject to a merger, consolidation or acquisition, it would become necessary for us to transfer your Personal Information to a third party, and in such case Centrepoint would require that the third party handles your Personal Information with no less care than taken by us.
    3. The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates related to your order. It may also be used to respond to your enquiries and requests. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you'll receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. You can unsubscribe from our email list at any time by following the instructions included at the bottom of each email, or by contacting us via our Participating Website.
    4. Other than as may be required in order to operate the Participating Website, or as otherwise described in the Participating Website Terms and Conditions or these Terms, we disclose your Personal Information to third parties only as reasonably required to protect the rights and safety of ourselves and Participating Website users or as required by law enforcement authorities. Centrepoint's operational purposes include, without limitation: 
      1. Centrepoint use of other companies and/or individuals to perform functions on its behalf (e.g. processing credit card payments, providing customer service, domestic or international data hosting/storage services on cloud or otherwise), and in such circumstances these companies or individuals will be provided access to only such Personal Information required to fulfill their functions (and only on the agreement that they not use your Personal Information for any other purposes); and
      2. Purposes intended to deliver publications to you, verify your account information, verify access to publications, determine whether you meet the minimum system requirements for use of the Service, provide you tailored content and instructions, targeted promotions, provide customer support, and seek your input regarding Centrepoint and the Participating Website.
    5. To keep your Personal Information safe, we ensure that sensitive and private data exchanges between you and Participating Website happen over a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)-secured communication channel, and are encrypted and protected with digital signatures. SSL-secured communication channels are specially designed to protect personal and sensitive information (payment details), which is sent over the internet.
    6. Apart from aforesaid, we may use third party service providers to help us operate our business, the Participating Website, or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We will only share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes if you've given us your permission to do so.
    7. You may review or update the Personal Information that Centrepoint holds in respect of your account by contacting Centrepoint at support@centrepointstores.com.

  5. **Treatment of General Information:** Centrepoint also collects your General Information to allow us, amongst other things, to better understand our users and improve the layout and functionality of the Participating Website. Centrepoint may use and disclose anonymous information, including aggregate anonymous information derived from your Personal Information, to inform publishers, partners, trusted affiliates, advertisers, and other interested parties as to the usage habits or characteristics of Centrepoint's customer base, and to serve any other business purposes.

  6. **Cookies:**
    1. Centrepoint may use cookies, or other technologies, to remember Personal Information or General Information when you use the Participating Website. Cookies are small files or records that Centrepoint may place on your web browser for collecting information about your activities on the Participating Website, preparing reports, assessing trends, in order to determine relevant interest based advertisements to serve the customers and otherwise monitoring the way in which the Participating Website is being used. Centrepoint may also use services hosted by third parties, to assist for these matters which may collect information, such as your IP address, sent by your browser or via cookies. This is intended to enhance convenience for you, and to assist Centrepoint to run an efficient operation.

    2. The use of cookies is relatively standard. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, if you prefer not to store cookies, you can choose to: 
      * not use Participating Site
      * set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie
      * set your browser to refuse to accept cookies
      * delete our cookies after visiting Participating Site
      * browse our site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting
By accepting the Terms, you confirm your consent to Centrepoint's use of cookies, and other such technologies, for these purposes.
  7. Any information that we collect and store that is personally identifiable is protected using appropriate means, and although Centrepoint does so, it will not be held responsible for any unauthorised access by third parties.

  8. The Participating Website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that Centrepoint is not responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites (Participating Websites excluded) not operated by Centrepoint, and cannot guarantee the security of any of your Personal Information collected there. Centrepoint encourages you to read the privacy statements of each and every third party website that collects your Personal Information.

  9. If you have any questions or feedback about the Privacy Policy, contact us at support@centrepointstores.com.

**Questions?:**

Contact us at 800-CPSTORES (800-6927)

By Post:    
Centrepoint (L.L.C)

Parcel ID 317-380

Store no: 8, Al Hamriya

PO Box 25030,

Dubai, UAE

Oops! There was a problem. Please correct the highlighted issues

Or via email

__Email entered is registered already

__Your recaptcha challenge answer is invalid. Please check and try again.

Or via email

__Your Username or Password is incorrect

__Your recaptcha challenge answer is invalid. Please check and try again.

__Your recaptcha challenge answer is invalid. Please check and try again.

We're sorry, we've run into a technical issue. Please try again later.
